So, when you're watching a movie like
Sinner's, just like your rapper brain,
like are you logging certain things or
is it okay?
>> [music]
>> I can watch a movie, I can watch a show,
and I'm always clocking something that
inspires me.
>> Another thing I love about hip-hop cuz
there's no really other genre where you
could reference so many things and then
make like these time capsules.
>> Yeah, hip-hop is so dense. I love that
hip-hop is being taught in universities.
It's no different than Odyssey or Homer
or anything like that. You could take
two bars and teach a whole class on,
just two bars, cuz it can be so layered.
>> I always say about hip-hop is like
there's no other genre in history where
you could say so many words in one song
or one album. And from a storytelling
perspective, you're just able to
communicate so much within it.
>> And even past words, like sonically,
samples.
>> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying? Like that's a
whole 'nother layer where you can
connect generation.
>> Makes me think of that scene in Sinner's
where he goes through the
history of music.
>> One of the greatest scenes ever done.
Like Ryan Coogler is he's a genius for
that. I I like to shed a tear when I saw
that. When we talk about the influence
of black music on all genres.
>> Yeah, to study music in America is to
study black music.
>> Exactly. Like
it was Ryan Coogler, my god.